NOUFAL RAHIM



CONTACT

+91 9778025976

noufal_b220444cs@nitc.ac.in

https://noufalrahim.vercel.app

in https://linkedin.com/in/noufalrahim

SKILLS

Web Development

React JS, Next JS, Node JS, Html, CSS, Javascript, Typescript, Git, Github

App Development

React Native, Javascript, Typescript, Git, Github

Data Structures and Algorithms

C, CPP

EDUCATION

B Tech in Computer Science and Engineering

National Institute of Technology Calicut

7.77

Higher Secondary

St. Antony's Public School Anakkal

93.6

Secondary

St. Antony's Public School Anakkal

98

AWARDS

Friday FOSSNight Hackathon Winner Qualified for NTSE Stage 2

PROFILE

I'm a dedicated student at NIT Calicut with expertise in web development using React JS, Next JS, Electron JS and Node JS. I also excel in app development with React Native and have solved over 200 questions on platforms like LeetCode, GeeksforGeeks, and HackerRank. I seek challenging roles to further enhance my knowledge and skills

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer Intern

Mapogo Ecommerce

December 2023 - June 2023

Contributed to the development of a startup application in react native

Web Developer Intern

National Institute of Technology, Calicut

June 2024 - July 2024

Contributed to the development of a frontend application for minor allotment process of upcoming batches

Web Developer Intern

Pentadots Solutions

October 2023 - December 2023

Contributed to the frontend development of a website for real estate company

Tech Head

FOSSCELL NITC

PROJECTS

Calculus

Calculus is a desktop accounting software for entrepreneurs, developed using Electron.js and Next.js. It streamlines daily sales and purchases management, enhancing business efficiency with a user-friendly interface and robust data handling capabilities.

.....

InsightLink

Insight Link is a cypher messaging app where users have to authenticate to view confidential messages. Developed using React Native, Gifted Chat, Socket.IO

Codelt

An online code editor platform Technologies used: React JS, Next JS, Monaco Text editor, Piston API

Website url: https://codeitnow.vercel.app

Rodents Gazette

Developed a newspaper website using React JS seamlessly fetching daily news from an external API.

Website url: https://therodentzgazette.netlify.app